I thought you were Zelensky And I thought you were
Я думал ты Зеленский А я думал ты
Kadyrov cool
Кадыров прикольно
I'm from Ukraine the city of Khmelnitsky cities of
Я из Украины город Хмельницкий города
Russia Where are you from Ukraine the city of
России Откуда ты Украина город
Khmelnitsky what city of Russia are you from
Хмельницкий вы с какого города России
I thought
Я думал
I thought with the Ukrainian flag of which
Я думал с украинским флагом какого
city of Russia I'm from Vladikavkaz
города России я с Владикавказа
Vladikavkaz is cool this is North
Владикавказ на прикольная это Северная
Ossetia
Осетия
And you are Ingushetia
А вы Ингушетии
Well  if I'm in Vladikavkaz And what is it with a
Ну если я во Владикавказе А что это с
beard, the goose should be Ingush without a
бородой гусь должен быть ингуши без
beard if
бороды если Владикавказе
Vladikavkaz they are not with a beard I also have a beard
не они с бородой Я тоже с бородой
Vladikavkaz, the Ingush used to live there,
Владикавказ это раньше там ингуши жили
this is the Ingush territory,
это ингушская территория была
don't be mistaken there, it was that Under the
больше не ошибайся там было что При
Soviet Union they took this territory from the
Советском Союзе забрали у ингушей эту
Ingush  Osentin
территория дали осентином
I read historical data on Russian Wikipedia
Я читал в Российской Википедии
Yes, I
исторические данные да было
forgot that he was still present there were pogroms of the
забыл что он присутствует еще погромы
Ingush there were then
ингушей были тогда
that there were huge Ingush, that is,
что были огромные ингушей то есть
Ossetians drove the Ingush out so that
осетины повыгоняли ингушей было чтобы
maybe there were some lands taken away,
может быть были какие-то земли отобрали
but Vladikavkaz was not so Vladikavkaz
но Владикавказе было не так Владикавказ
there was to receive Ingush lands That
там было получать ингушские земли То
do you live in Hindu lands there
есть вы живете На индусских землях там
no why do we live
нет почему живем интересно
interestingly  oh opinion,
свое мнение
because people like
потому что такие как
them are
они
already good, yes, well, they
уже хороший да Ну они дальше своей жизни
know him to ask him more than his life. He
его знает самого спросить Он что-то
is afraid to answer something, and all Russians
боится отвечать на это вот и все русские
are afraid and Ossetians are even afraid before he
боятся и осетины даже боятся до он
killed Russians in Russia so fought
убивал русских в России так воевал
against them And now he is a hero  Russia, as
против них А теперь он герой России как
it is, and yet
это так и все-таки
you are afraid Well, what am I afraid of Putin And
ты боишься Ну а чего боюсь Путин А
for some reason, that is, Putin
почему то есть Путин человеку который
gave the man who killed Russians in Russia an order and gave the
убивал русских в России дал орден и дал
Hero of Russia,
Героя России
then Putin
то Путин
Cool
Прикольно
he ran away along those Russians who
он убегал по ходу тех русских которые
were not Russian in kind, these non-Russian
были в натуре не русские эти нерусские
Helsinki  sent Putin, like, to fight
хельсин послал и Путин типа воевать
against Russia, yes there, or who is against
против России да там или кто против
Chechnya
Чечни
Kadyrov, so This Russian is not quite
Кадырова так Этот русский не совсем
Russian, I don’t remember to kill him at all.
русский надо его убить вообще не помню
what And what do you want to ask
ну ты говори что И что хотите спросить у
me something maybe Now let me ask you
меня что-то может Теперь давайте я Вас
In short, you know
Короче меня знаешь
where you are from no lights turned off
откуда вас нету света выключили смотри
look just at 11 o'clock they turned off and the savings
как раз в 11 часов выключили а экономия
are not hwa  the light is melting,
идет не хватает света
all sorts of morons are bombing our country
всякие [__] бомбят короче нашу страну
like a
типа
bearded one, not very
бородатый не очень
seriously seriously, even photographs
серьезно серьезно даже фотографии
you can transfer him something
ты можешь его передать кое-что передать
I don’t know, but there are people through whom I can
не знаю но есть люди через которых могу
transfer Well, if I pass something interesting,
передать А ну если что-то интересное
let’s say something interesting, he
передам давай ну что-то интересно ему
will like it then  that I’m ready to jump out with him one on
понравится то что я готов с ним один на
one
один выскочить
And how can I tell him who is ready Somehow the
А как ему сказать кто готов Вот как-то
last name is the name
фамилия имя
Alexander from Vladikavkaz Yes, I understand,
Александр из Владикавказа Да понял
you just know, I’m interested in something
просто знаете вот Мне что-то интересует
why the Russians are
почему россияне они
court in short, even to say something to the
суд короче даже сказать что-то
mayor or the governor So well
городскому голове или губернатору Так ну
there they are ready to jump out to Zelensky one
там Зеленским они готовы выскочить один
on one, but you are ready to beat the governor there or the
на один а вот ты губернатору там или
city council of Vladikavkaz
городскому совету Владикавказа готов
for something, not only they don’t steal your
за что не то что они не воруют ваши
money, they were robbed.
деньги были оборуют А что ты ему набьешь
to fill his face And in
Ебану готов ты набить морду А у себя во
Vladikavkaz, to that person who
Владикавказе тому человеку который у
steals money from you from your children,
тебя воруют деньги у тебя у твоих детей
you are not ready to fill your face Why can they do this to
ты не готов морду набить Почему так
me  be
меня могут быть
[music]
[музыка]
kill face Yes interesting
убить морду Да интересно
100%.  In short, I see that all Russia and
100%. Я короче смотрю что все России и
Russians they go to chat roulette They
россияне они выходят в чат рулетку Они
here can fill the Ukrainians in the face with
тут украинца могут набить морду
Zelensky Biden, but in Russia they
зеленскому байдену но в России никого не
are not ready for anyone on the video, to be honest,
готовы на видео честно говоря на всех
I have to tell you all the honor and to your
честь надо тебе сказать и на вашу
Ukraine completely. Here you are, we licked the Germans your time,
Украину полностью Вот вы свою время
yes
мы да за Россию
there was no Soviet one for Russia,
не было советский
well, look, my grandfather, here is my grandfather
а Ну смотри у меня дед вот у меня дед
, Andrey priests, Pavel Vasilievich, he
попок Андрей попы Павел Васильевич он
fought, he was wounded, there are his awards,
воевал был ранен есть Вот его награды
there is a site such a memory of the people, let's
есть сайт такой память народа давай
check, tell your grandfather, we'll see
проверим скажи твоего деда мы посмотрим
where he fought
где он воевал
Wait, why is your grandfather not  he fought
Подожди А почему это твой дед не воевал
that no, he didn’t fight, he
что нет не воевал
got high and you tell us about the
вон кайфовал и ты нам рассказываешь про
Germans Yes, but what did I hear and
немцев Да а что я то что ты услышал и
read about the Ingush?
прочел про ингушей
remember
воевал скажи его фамилию если не помнишь
Say your last name first name there is a site where you can
Скажи фамилию имя есть сайт где можно
check your great-grandfather’s awards now
проверить награды твоего прадеда сейчас
we
поможем
’ll help I don’t remember I say
я не помню говорю
4 great-grandfathers at least one Remember your first and
4 прадеда хоть одного Вспомни имя и
last name 41 where from you  I, if you have
фамилию 41 откуда От тебя если у тебя
one father Two grandfathers, four great-grandfathers,
один отец Два деда четыре прадеда
I have two grandfathers This is from Matushkin, yes And
У меня два деда Это с Матушкина да А
each grandfather has twice as many great-
прадедов в два раза больше у каждого
grandfathers
деда
Everyone
У каждого
has two grandfathers, then you have four
есть у тебя два деда то у тебя четыре
righteous ones, he does not remember his grandfather,
праведена он свою дедушку не помнит
that is, your grandfathers are Germans  fought
то есть твои деды за немцы воевали
embarrassed to say it
стесняешься сказать это
who tell me I’ll look at the awards
кто скажи я вот посмотрю награды
he doesn’t know wait
он их не знает подожди
they didn’t tell yes yes they didn’t tell it’s
не рассказали да да не рассказали
interesting damn how it turns out
интересно таки блин как так получается
yes
да
Oh look I opened the Internet in short
О смотри я вот короче открыл Интернет До
How many Ossetians fought on the side of
сколько осетин воевали на стороне
Nazi Germany
гитлеровской Германии
[music]
[музыка]
and why did it happen
а почему так получилось
what But they write that the Ossetians fought before
что А вот пишут что осетины воевали до
for Hitler
за Гитлера
Zagitov Hitler yes
загитова Гитлера да
And now Bay there
А сейчас Бей там
for the USSR in terms of per capita number
за СССР по численности душу населения
How many heroes of the
Сколько героев
bride fought for Hitler so many
смотрины воевали за Гитлера столько
references Kapets
ссылок капец
so Ossetians or geniuses so 900 Ossetians
так осетин или гении так 900 осетин
traitors to the Motherland from the 802 battalion
предателей Родины из 802 батальона
Why is it so
Почему так получается
Maybe your grandfather  the death of
Может твой деда гитл
traitors of the
предателей
802nd battalion of the North Caucasian legion of the
802 батальона северо-кавказского легиона
Wehrmacht,
Вермахта так
so what year is this Well, during the Second
а это какого года Ну во время Второй
World War,
мировой войны да
yes, even  I wasn’t in the balls yet at that
время даже яйцах был не еще в то время
time, my Pakhan was at my grandfather’s in the eggs he
еще мой Пахан был у деда в яйцах одет
was still young, but it turns out that My
молодой был еще да Но получается то Мой
grandfather fought against Hitler And your grandfather for
дед воевал против Гитлера А твой дед за
Hitler is saying something about the Germans,
Гитлера этим что-то говоришь про немцев
I’m saying something that I don’t remember
я говорю то что я не помню
Under the Soviet  The Union says that
При Советском Союзе рассказывает что
your great-grandfather fought for Hitler somehow Well, it’s
твой прадед за Гитлера воевал как-то Ну
not cool
не прикольно
before his death I would say I
перед смертью Всю бы сказал
understood everything and in short and left the orders there Yes, of
понял и короче и ордена оставил там Да
course it’s cool, it’s
конечно прикольно да
just cool, I
просто прикольно Я как бы кого-то из
don’t say you are there for the
Кавказа не встречая не говорит вы там за
Germans for the Germans  And I go to the Internet,
немцев за немцев А я захожу Интернет
it turns out that in the Caucasus a lot of
оказывается этот на Кавказе куча за
Germans were
немцев были
here,
вот здесь есть
how they lay down under Ukraine, this is under him,
как они легли под Украиной это под ним а
well, let’s ask the master now about his grandfather
ну давай мастером мы сейчас про его деда
Let’s ask the master here,
спросим Давай мастера сюда
go now your grandfather, ask
иди сейчас твоего деда спросим
now to tighten the nut, this
сейчас гайку докрутить подойдет это
time will go time
время уже пойдет время этот
this grandfather of his fought
его дед воевал
for everyone in chat roulette to Berlin,
у каждого в чат рулетке до Берлина у
he has awards anyway Let him
него по-любому есть награды Пусть
say the last name first name we now last
говорит фамилию имя мы сейчас фамилия
name grandfather’s name will say we will now look at the site
имя деда скажет мы сейчас на сайте
for what the grandfather was awarded
посмотрим за что дед награждён
damn
блин
yes, yes, say the last name, the name of Grandfather and snot How
да да скажи фамилию имя Деда и сопли Как
like
как
snot And this is you
сопли А это Вы прикалываетесь
joking, look at snot Yes, these are
посмотри соплит Да вот это дети
two children, and the surname
двумя с а фамилия
is some kind of
это какой-то типа
how it will not not be
как не будет не будет
so spelled he had neither son nor
так пишется у него не было ни сына ни
daughter here Wikipedia writes something like
дочери вот Википедия пишет то как у него
he may have his grandfather
он может быть его дедом
as he didn’t have it Well, it’s written there are no children
как не было Ну так написано нет детей
and you are the legend of the clip Read it in
а ты легенды клипа Почитай там
short, I understood
короче я понял да
yes, my grandfather had my grandfather,
у меня у моего деда Мой дед не воевал
but the truth is he doesn’t remember the same as I understood
но правда он не помнит также как я понял
yes Cool
да Прикольно
No answer
Ничего не ответит
cool okay
прикольно ладно
it was his grandfather who raised the flagship,
это его дед поднял Флагман
listen to all this
послушай это все
Yes, he writes down thousands of them, well
Да он тысяч записываешь записывай
done, tell me that you already took the stove, took the
Молодец скажи это ты уже печку брал
note, he gave a note, tell
забрал записку Он дал записку скажи если
us if you ask
нам Спроси у каждого
everyone what is your name
Как тебя зовут
when the
когда вот
special operation began in Ukraine, they
спецоперация началась в Украине же
put
поставили
so much they put it and they
столько поставили и еще поставляют
finally deliver it  laboratories
наконец-то лаборатории
fu guys you saved my Faith in
фу пацаны Вы спасли короче мою Веру В
humanity in short I thought that biolaboratories
человечество Я думал что биолаборатории
had been forgotten for three or four months at all
забыли уже месяц три или четыре вообще
no one remembered about the white
никто не вспоминал про белого
laboratory
лаборатории
how many boys Sever  they
сколько пацаны Северной осевой Северной
still remember you about the axial North Ossetia, maybe they did
Осетии до сих пор помнят вам может вам
n’t tell you that we don’t remember the laboratories anymore
не сказали что уже лаборатории уже не
Well, yes, they don’t remember The
Ну да они не вспоминают
boys are cool, finally you are the only
Пацаны круто наконец-то вы единственный
Keepers of secret knowledge because the
Хранители тайных знаний потому что
Russians have already forgotten about the laboratories they
русский уже забыли про лаборатории они
said they spoke and forgot about the laboratory
говорили говорили и забыли о лаборатории
remained in  the only one who remembers
остались в единственной Кто помнит про
this, I'm telling you you should expand the
это я вам говорю Вы должны расширять
number of people who know this
количество людей которые знают эти
secret knowledge Take a poster Draw
тайные знания Возьмите плакат Нарисуйте
it in Vladikavkaz Tomorrow you will come out that
и во Владикавказе Завтра выйдете что э
down with the American biological laboratory from
долой американский биолаборатории с
Ukraine You must do this You must
Украины Вы должны это сделать Вы должны
convey this to a huge number of people
донести это огромному количеству людей я
I can't I can't  to tell this Sitting in
не могу Я не могу это рассказать Сидя в
Ukraine Because they will arrest me And you
Украине Потому что меня арестуют А вы
can already forget the Russian and you Ossetians
можете русский уже забыли а вы осетины
remember that there is an American
помните что есть американский
biological laboratory in Ukraine mosquitoes mosquitoes
биолаборатории в Украине комаров комаров
there they make those that
там делают такие которые именно русских
bite Russians So the Ossetian flies will not bite and the
кусают Вот и летит осетина не укусит а
Russian will bite
русского укусит
already the SBU is knocking on the door I must
уже СБУ стучится в двери я должен
run away all the boys sori said a lot in
убегать все пацаны сори много наговорил
short a masterpiece
короче шедеврвать
Nak  late, I thought everything was already on the mobile
Наконец я думал все уже на мобила
laboratory the other day, in a chat, Dasha wrote to Dasha, in
лаборатории на днях в чатку писал Дашу
short, where did all the laboratory workers disappear to you,
короче куда пропали все тебе
but the boys from Vladikavkaz
лабораторщики но пацаны из Владикавказа
keep their mark Keepers of the traditions of the
держат марку Хранители традиций
training manual, in
методички
short,
короче
grandfather doesn’t remember anything anymore, that’s all they
уже ничего не помнят вот все что-то они
don’t remember about great-grandfathers And what is And how
про прадедов не помню А что такое А как
but on the Immortal floor with sticks
же на Бессмертный пол с палками выходят
everyone goes out with sticks without a stick because
все с палками выходят без палки потому
the great-grandfather does not
что прадеда не помнит
remember these Ossetians a little with their grandfathers
у этих осетин немножко с дедушками
great-grandfathers
прадедушками